It's raining cats and dogs out there!
I hope they make it back all right.
Heads up! Andy's coming!
Andy, time for dinner.
Yes! I'm starving!
Don't forget to wash your hands!
Okay, Mom!
- Do you see him? - No.
Well, he's done for.
He'll be lost! Forever!
Jessie. Buzz. Slink. Molly's room.
The rest of you, stay put.
Bo!
Situation?
Lost toy. Side yard.
Billy. Goat. Gruff. Raise the blinds.
They have names?
You never told me that.
You never asked.
Where is he?
There!
How do we reach him?
Operation Pull-Toy!
- Slink! - You got it, Woody!
Barbies!
Go!
Flashlight.
Hang on, R.C.!
I ain't got any more slink!
It's beautiful.
I'm so glad to see this old lamp go to a good home.
We've had it since Molly was a baby.
Molly, are you sure it's all right?
- Yeah, I don't want it anymore. - Thank you.
Where's Woody?
Yeah, hi. I think I left my keys here.
- Woody. - Quick!
We'll sneak in the hedges before he's back.
Woody, it's okay.
What? No! No, no, no. You can't go!
- What's best for Andy is that... - Woody.
I'm not Andy's toy.
What?
It's time for the next kid.
And thank you again for everything.
I really appreciate it.
My pleasure. I'm glad it all worked out.
You know,
kids lose their toys every day.
Sometimes they get left in the yard or...
put in the wrong box.
And that box gets taken away.
Mom, where's Woody?
Andy! Come inside!
I can't find Woody!
Well, good night.
Goodbye. Drive safe.
There you are.
Mom, I found him! I found him!
Oh, good. Come on and get inside.
♪ You've got a friend in me ♪
You've Got a Friend In Me - Randy Newman
Reach for the sky!
♪ You've got a friend in me ♪
Ride 'em, cowboy!
♪ When the road looks rough ahead ♪
♪ And you're miles and miles from your nice warm bed ♪
There's a snake in my boot.
♪ You just remember what your old pal said ♪
♪ Boy, you've got a friend in me ♪
To infinity and beyond!
♪ Yeah, you've got a friend in me ♪
♪ Now, some other folks might be a little bit smarter than I am ♪
My cowboy!
♪ Big and stronger, too ♪
Woody, let's go!
♪ Maybe ♪
♪ But none of them will ever love you the way I do ♪
You're my favorite deputy!
♪ It's me and you, boy ♪
♪ And as the years go by ♪
♪ Our friendship will never die ♪
♪ You're gonna see it's our destiny ♪
They've escaped and they're headed right for us!
♪ You've got a friend in me ♪
Full speed ahead!
It's getting hot in here!
- Where's my ear? - You're on my foot!
Quit shoving.
- Sorry! That was my horn. - Could you move over a bit, please?
To infinity and beyond!
I know that was you, Potato Head.
Everyone, listen. I thought I told you...
when Mom quickly cleans the bedroom like that...
expect to be put in the closet.
How much longer?
Keep it to a dull roar, Rex.
Deep breaths, Jessie. Deep breaths.
Settle down, Slink.
Sit. Good boy!
Sheriff, do I need to be worried?
No, no. My guys are veterans. They'll hang in there.
Good. Just keep them calm until we get word.
Yes, ma'am.
How are you, uh, feeling about today?
Good, good. Yeah, good.
I'm good.
Good.
We're on! Bonnie's done with breakfast!
- Any minute now. - You hear that?
Any minute now.
Wind 'em if you got 'em.
Keep your batteries clean, your joints unlocked...
Thanks, Woody. I got it.
Yes, I'm sorry. You're right, you're right.
The town is open!
Hi, Mayor!
Banker!
Hi, Ice-Cream Man! Hi, Hat Shop Owner!
Mailman!
And the sheriff!
Okay. Bye, toys!
Sheriff Jessie!
Giddy-up, Bullseye!
They went that way!
Chase them!
What a beautiful hat shop!
- You have so many hats... - Wow. They're doing "Hat Shop."
When's the last time we ever got to play that?
Remember when she played "House"?
I liked "House."
Those were the days.
It was basic.
You made a house, you lived in it, done.
That's the third time you haven't been picked this week.
I don't know. I don't keep count.
You don't have to.
- I'll do it for you. - Okay, okay, okay, I get it.
- It's been a while. - Oh, looky there.
You got your first dust bunny.
How adorable.
What you gonna name it?
What about Dusty?
- Francis! - Harry!
- Karen! - Fuzzball!
- LeBron. - No, Fluffy.
- How about Thumper? - Tumbleweed!
"Tumbleweed." Oh, that's good. That's good.
He's a cowboy, so that makes a lot of sense.
So many choices.
I just can't decide!
Bonnie?
What are you doing? We got to go.
You don't wanna be late for kindergarten orientation, do you?
But... I don't wanna go.
We talked about this.
We're gonna meet your teachers,
- see your classroom... - Can I bring a toy?
Toys don't go to school, that's the rule.
Freeze! Nobody move!
Bonnie always forgets something.
She'll be back any second.
That goes for you, too, Hamm.
But it's money!
You all right, Woody?
I'm sure she'll pick you next time.
Come on, I'm fine. No problem.
Woody. Here.
Thanks, Jessie.
We're here for you, buddy.
- I don't want to play the baker. - Pricklepants.
- The hat shop owner is the role I was born to play! - Okay.
All right, Pricklepants, back to your bakery.
Excuse me, Dolly?
Woody, can't you see I'm threatening everyone?
- Go back to the closet. - Yeah, I know. I know. It's just...
I'm worried about Bonnie.
A toy should go with her to orientation.
Didn't you hear Dad? You'll get Bonnie in trouble.
Yeah, but kindergarten is so different.
It can be too much for a kid.
Having a buddy with them to get through it
can really help things.
I remember with Andy, I would go to school with him...
I'm sorry, Woody. I hate to sound like a broken record.
But Bonnie is not Andy.
No, no, no, of course, I get that.
- But if you would just... - Places, everyone!
Bonnie?
What are you doing back there?
Come on, we have to go.
That's my big girl.
Come on. We got to hurry, okay?
Don't forget your backpack.
You're gonna have so much fun.
All right. Now what was it you were saying, Woody?
Woody?
Here we are.
Bonnie, honey, it'll be okay.
Hi! Are you Bonnie?
My name is Miss Wendy.
I'm going to be your kindergarten teacher.
We have a special place where you can put your backpack.
You want to see?
Here we are, Bonnie. Just for you.
Okay, class,
let's all find a seat at a table...
so we can start craft time.
On the first day of school,
you'll need a place to put your pencils.
So, today, we're going to make pencil holders.
Now, everyone take a cup...
and we'll use the art supplies to decorate them.
Hi.
Bonnie. That is so clever.
"Hello, I'm Forky. Nice to meet you!"
Well, hello, Forky, it's nice to meet you.
I'm Miss Wendy.
Mom! Dad! Look what I made!
His name is Forky!
That is so cool!
I finished kindergarten!
No. That was just orientation.
But for being such a brave girl,
we have a surprise for you.
What is it?
Since school doesn't start for another week,
we are going on a road trip!
- Can I bring Forky? - 'Course you can!
Yay!
And they said I shouldn't go to school with Bonnie.
We got this kindergarten thing under control, eh?
I can't believe I'm talking to a spork.
Hi, toys!
Bye, toys!
He did go to kindergarten!
- I knew it. - No, no, no, guys, listen...
You tryin' to get Bonnie in trouble?
No, of course not!
You could have been confiscated.
- What does that mean - Taken away.
- No! - Or worse.
You could've been lost!
No, no, no, guys, listen.
Bonnie had a great day in class...
and we're going on a road trip.
- Road trip - Vacation!
But then something really weird happened.
Bonnie made a friend in class.
- What a kid. - Oh, she's already making friends.
No, no. She literally made a new friend.
It's okay.
Come on out. That's it.
Come on, there you go.
Come on, let's get you out of there.
You got this.
Good. Good.
Everyone, I want you to meet Forky.
- Golly Bob howdy! - Look at that!
Look how long his arms are!
- Trash? - No.
No, toys.
They're all toys.
T-Toy... Trash.
No, no, no.
That's the trash.
These are your friends.
Hi!
Trash!
- No, no, it's okay. - Trash!
Woody, I have a question.
Well, actually, not just one,
I have all of them.
I have all the questions.
Why does he want to go to the trash?
- Because he was made from trash. - Trash!
Look, I know this is a little strange, but
- you got to trust me on this. - Trash?
Forky is the
most important toy to Bonnie right now.
Important?
He's a spork.
Yes. Yeah, I know, but this spork...
this toy is crucial to Bonnie
getting adjusted to kindergarten.
Woody, aren't you being a little dramatic about all this?
I know this is new to everybody...
but you should see how much
this little guy means to Bonnie.
When she started playing with him...
she had the biggest smile on her face.
I wish you could have seen it.
Bonnie was really upset...
and I swear, once she made Forky...
it was a complete transformation.
- Woody? - Just a second, Jessie.
So, we all have to make sure nothing happens to him.
Something happened to him.
Chutes and Ladders!
- Trash. - No, no, no! No! No!
You're a toy now, Forky! Come on!
Stop! Stop it!
- No, no, no! Come on! - Trash!
Trash! Trash!
Well, I guess I'll just babysit him
till he's used to the room.
Forky?
Where are you, Forky?
There you are!
I thought I'd lost you, silly.
No, no, no.
Big girl scary!
Like I said before, Bonnie's not scary.
She loves you and you need to...
Forky?
Bonnie!
Let's go!
Rise and shine!
Who wants to go on a road trip?
Me! I'm gonna bring Dolly, and Buttercup...
and Forky, and...
Forky Where are you?
He's got to be here somewhere.
Forky?
Forky!
Come on. Let's eat some breakfast and hit the road!
Let's go, Forky!
He's quite a handful, Woody.
You need help with him on the road trip?
No. No, no. I got it, I got it.
We'll just be stuck in an RV.
He can't get far. I got this.
I got it.
♪ I can't let you ♪
I Can't Let You Throw Yourself Away - Randy Newman
♪ I can't let you throw yourself away ♪
♪ I can't let you ♪
♪ Don't you want to see the sun come up each morning ♪
No, no!
♪ Don't you want to see the sun go down each day ♪
♪ Don't you want to see that little girl that loves you so ♪
♪ Her heart would break ♪
Oh, yeah!
♪ If you should go ♪
♪ I can't let you ♪
♪ I can't let you throw yourself away. ♪
No, no, no!
No! No! No!
♪ So it seems to me like you're never gonna behave yourself ♪
♪ Since I'm not gonna do this every day ♪
♪ Come tomorrow, you're gonna have to save yourself ♪
♪ Got nothing more to say ♪
♪ You're not listening anyway ♪
♪ I can't let you ♪
♪ I can't let you throw yourself away ♪
Trash, here I come!
Come on.
♪ I can't let you ♪
♪ I can't let you throw yourself away ♪
I don't wanna be a toy!
♪ I can't let you ♪
♪ I can't let you throw yourself away ♪
Hey, buddy.
Hey, Buzz.
You doing okay?
I don't know, Buzz.
I know you weren't around when Andy was little... but
I don't remember it being this hard.
Want me to take the next watch?
I'll keep an eye on Forky.
No, no. I need to do this.
That little voice inside me
would never leave me alone if I gave up.
Who do you think it is?
Who?
The voice inside of you. Who do you think it is?
Me?
You know, my conscience?
That part of you that tells you things?
What you're really thinking?
Fascinating.
So, your inner voice advises you.
What?
It's a secret mission in uncharted space.
Let's go.
Where's Forky?
Oh, no! Forky!
Forky!
I am not a toy!
I'm a spork.
Be quiet!
I was made for soup, salad...
maybe chili, and then the trash.
I'm litter!
Freedom!
Hamm, how far to our next stop?
5.32 miles, give or take.
I can make that.
I'll meet you at the RV park.
Woody, hold on a minute. Woody!
Forky!
Forky, where are you?
- Carry me - No.
Why do I have to be a toy?
Because you have Bonnie's name
written on the bottom of your sticks.
Why do I have Bonnie's name
written on the bottom of my sticks?
Because she...
Look, she plays with you all the time, right?
Yes.
And who does she sleep with every night?
The big white fluffy thing?
No, not her pillow.
You.
All right, Forky.
You have to understand how lucky you are right now.
You're Bonnie's toy.
You are going to help create happy memories...
that will last for the rest of her life.
What?
Okay. Doing it for Bonnie.
Doing this for Bonnie, you're doing it for Bonnie.
Okay, like it or not, you are a toy.
Maybe you don't like being one,
but you are one nonetheless.
Which means you are going to be there for Andy when he...
Who's Andy?
I mean, Bonnie.
You have to be there for Bonnie.
That is your job.
Well, what's your job?
Well, right now, it's to make sure you do yours.
- Carry me - No.
Who's Andy?
Andy was my other kid.
You had another kid?
Yeah, yeah.
For a long time.
And it was pretty great.
I was a favorite toy, actually.
Running the room was my job.
Keeping all the toys in place...
So, he thought Andy's room was a planet?
- That is messed up. - Right!
That's exactly what I thought when he first showed up.
Yeah. I mean, how is that not annoying?
- Thank you! - Seriously, that is the...
Well, then you watch 'em grow up
and become a full person.
And then they leave.
They go off and do things you'll never see.
Don't get me wrong, you still feel good about it.
But then somehow you find yourself,
after all those years...
sitting in a closet just feeling...
Useless?
Yeah.
Your purpose fulfilled?
Exactly.
Woody, I know what your problem is.
You do?
You're just like me.
Trash!
What is it with you and trash?
- It's warm. - Ew.
- It's cozy. - I guess.
And safe!
Like somebody's whispering in your ear,
"Everything's gonna be okay."
Forky, that's it.
That's how Bonnie feels when she's with you.
- She does - Yes!
Wait a sec.
- You mean she thinks I'm warm? - Yep.
- And cozy - Uh-huh.
And sometimes kinda squishy?
Well, that, too. Yes.
I get it now.
I'm Bonnie's trash.
Yes! Wait, what?
I am Bonnie's trash!
No, no, no, not exactly.
She must be feeling awful without me.
Woody, we got to get going, she needs me!
Hey, Bonnie, I'm coming!
Forky, slow down! Forky!
Bonnie, I'm coming!
Forky!
Forky, look. Bonnie's right over there.
Hurry!
Woody?
Bo?
Aren't we, aren't we going to Bonnie?
I know, I know. But my friend might be in there.
Friend?
A friend, uh... Well, a friend is...
Well, a friend is like you and me.
- Trash - Trash, like... Yes.
And I'm very worried that she might be lost.
But, Woody, Bonnie's right there.
Yeah, we'll have you back before she wakes up. Come on.
Bo?
Bo.
Bo, Bo, Bo...
- Bo? - Bo?
Can we go back to Bonnie now?
I don't see your friend.
Yeah, okay.
She's not in here.
Come on, let's go.
Is that Bo?
Hey, howdy.
Hey there.
Sorry to bother you, but...
Why, you're not a bother at all.
We were just out for my early morning stroll.
And look... we met you!
My name is Gabby Gabby.
And this is my very good friend Benson.
Woody. Pleasure to meet you.
Well, it's nice to meet you, Woody. And you are...?
This is Forky.
I'm trash.
Our kid made him.
Kid? Toys around here don't have kids.
Are you two lost?
Lost No, no.
But we are looking for a lost toy.
She's a figurine. Used to be on that lamp in the window?
Name's Bo Peep?
Bo Peep?
- Oh, yes, I know Bo. - You do?
Hop on in. We'll take you to her.
You don't have to do that.
Well, okay.
Benson, be careful with our new friends.
What service.
Thank you for your help.
I haven't seen Bo in years.
May I ask, when were you made?
Me?
I'm not sure. Late '50s?
Me, too!
Gee, I wonder if we were made in the same factory.
Wouldn't that be something?
I got to say, you are in great condition.
Well, I try to stay active.
And look at that,
you have a voice box like me.
Benson, show him.
That's really not necessary.
I'm Gabby Gabby
and I love you.
You need to fix that.
My record works just fine.
It's the voice box that's broken.
Does yours still work?
There's a snake in my boot!
Listen to that! Let's see it.
I bet it's the same type.
No, thanks, mine's sewn inside.
Is Bo around here? Because we need...
The store is about to open.
Don't worry, we'll take you where no one will see us.
Oh, no. We can't stay.
Yes, you can.
We got to go.
You can't leave yet. You have what I need.
Right inside there.
Returned that lamp the next day.
You're kidding me!
Mom, can we go to the park now?
Harmony!
Stop him, please.
What's going on?
Come on! Let's go!
He's coming, he's coming! I see him!
Forky We got to get out of...
Woody!
I'd like to join your posse, boys.
But first, I'm gonna sing a little song.
Grandma, look what I found.
- Can I take it to the park - Sure.
Mom, she has enough toys from the store.
It's fine. Nobody buys the toys anyway.
Thanks, Grandma!
Mom, can we go to the carnival?
We're going to the park.
Maybe later, sweetie.
Any sign of Woody?
I don't see him!
Maybe we should have gone with the fork.
The spoon is safer.
Forky?
Where's Forky?
Mom! Dad!
- What's wrong, honey? - Are you okay?
I can't find Forky! He's missing!
Bonnie, it'll be all right.
I'm sure he's here somewhere.
You know, if you don't find him,
you can make a new one.
No! There's only one Forky!
Let's go look outside.
Maybe he fell on the ground somewhere.
Poor Bonnie.
We're gonna find him, okay?
We have to find him, Mom. He needs me.
Woody was right.
We all should have been safeguarding the utensil.
Why isn't Woody back yet?
Do you think he's lost?
Buzz, what do we do?
What do we do, Buzz?
- What do we do, Buzz Buzz! - I, uh...
- Buzz. - What would Woody do?
Jump out of a moving vehicle.
What would Woody do?
It's a secret mission in uncharted space.
Let's go!
I think I have to go.
- Where - Where you goin' Why?
Should we all go?
- Are we going? - And then what?
No time to explain! Attack!
No time to explain!
- Oh, no! - Buzz!
Okay, what is with everyone jumping out the window?
Woody and Forky were last seen on the highway.
But where is the highway?
The slingshot maneuver is all we've got!
Full speed ahead!
Thanks, inner voice!
The highway.
On my way, Woody!
Rad.
Step right up!
Put your money down!
Get yourself a real Buzz Lightyear!
Harmony, honey. Sunscreen.
Okay.
Be right back, Mr. Cowboy.
Okay. Antique store, antique store...
That way!
Did you see 'em? How many are there?
We got a busload of campers!
Here they come!
Playtime, baby!
Baby! It's a good day to play, huh?
Am I right?
"Hello, Mr. Cowboy. How are you today?"
"Do you like riding horses?"
Wanna play on the swings?
Wait for me!
Bo?
Come on.
Bo!
I can't believe it's you!
Bo Peep!
I never thought I'd see you again!
- So, which kid is yours? - Which one is yours?
- None. - No one.
- Wait, you're a lost toy? - You're a lost toy?
- That's great. - That's awful.
I mean, awfully great...
that you are lost out here.
- Skunk, skunk, skunk! - Watch out!
I told you not to drive so fast.
You almost ran him over.
Hey, guys!
Hold on there!
Okay! I missed you, too.
If it isn't Bobby Gus?
Lefty?
Billy, Goat, and Gruff.
Right! Right! Right! Sorry, guys.
- Girls. - Girls! Of course!
All right, all right.
Okay, let's get a look at you. You need any repairs?
Repairs No, I'm fine.
Nice find, girls.
Where did you get all this stuff?
Here and there.
You know, some kids play rougher than others...
so I try to be prepared.
How long have you been out on your own?
Seven fantastic years!
Seven?
You would not believe the things I've seen.
No.
Gigs.
Come on out. There's someone I want you to meet.
Be right down.
What's the situation? We heading out of town or...
Who's this?
You remember the rag doll I told you about?
- The cowboy - Yep!
No way!
- Don't stare. - I'm totally staring.
Woody, this is Giggle McDimples.
Hi, Giggle.
You didn't tell me he was a cop.
Howdy, Sheriff.
Officer Giggle McDimples.
I run Pet Patrol for Mini-Opolis.
Yeah, search and rescue.
Ants, caterpillars,
miniature poodles, spiders.
Carl! Where you headed?
Combat Carl just heard there's a birthday party...
at the playground on Main Street.
Rumor has it they got two pinatas.
- That could be 20 to 30 kids. - Nice!
Oh, yeah! Combat Carl's gettin' played with!
You guys in?
You bet! Woody, you are gonna love this!
No, I can't, sir.
Bo, I need to get back to my kid.
What?
You got a kid?
Yeah.
Way to beat the odds, soldier.
Meet you at the playground, Peep.
Combat Carl's got a pinata party to crash.
All right, move out. Hut! Hut! Hut!
So, you're, uh, with a kid?
It's not Andy, is it?
No, no, no. He went off to college.
But he gave us to Bonnie.
- You have a little girl. - No way!
Yeah, yeah. It's why I'm out here.
Her other toy is trapped
in this antique store, and I have to...
Second Chance Antiques?
We know that store.
That's great. That is great!
If you know the store, you could really
- help me find him... - No way.
We wasted years there,
just sitting on the shelf, collecting dust.
Bo, that's awful.
But I don't have a choice.
I have to get that toy from Gabby.
Steer clear of that weirdo.
If I were you, I'd cut my losses and go home.
But Bonnie needs him to get through kindergarten.
Kids lose toys every day. Bonnie will get over it.
No, no...
You see, Bonnie needs him just like Molly needed you.
No. Sorry, girls.
Molly's not here.
Molly Bo, I didn't know you had a kid.
That was a long time ago.
Bo's kid was something special.
She was the cutest thing...
but so afraid of the dark.
It was just a phase.
You weren't there in the beginning.
Hearing Molly cry each night...
it broke every toy's heart.
And then, Bo came into the room.
Her lamp was the only thing that made Molly feel safe.
Mom would let her keep Bo on all night.
Ha! Who knew you were such a softy?
And Molly would fall asleep
with her hand resting on Bo's feet.
Okay! Okay. I get it.
Bo, my kid really needs this toy.
Will you help me? For old times' sake.
All right, all right.
Thank you!
- Thank you! - All right.
Guess we're doing this. Let's ride!
Second Chance Antiques, and step on it.
Benson, are we finished?
That feels great!
Look at that! Good as new.
Yeah. Thank you, uh, Benson.
So, um, when's Woody coming back?
Like I said, soon.
He won't forget about you.
How do you know?
You have your child's name written on your feet.
Sticks.
That makes you a very important toy.
That's exactly what Woody says.
Interesting.
Hi, Grandma! We're back!
She's back.
Who is she?
Harmony.
Wait a second... she took Woody.
Did she lose him?
No. My Harmony is perfect.
Forky, it's tea time. It's tea time.
What is tea time?
I'll show you.
A little bit of milk, two lumps of sugar.
I've been practicing. How do I look?
A little higher.
Stick out your pinky.
Nice!
Delicious!
Harmony, sweetie, I'm leaving.
Come give me a hug.
Bye, Mom. I love you.
When my voice box is fixed...
I'll finally get my chance.
Now, about our friend Woody.
I wanna know everything about him.
Oh, yeah, Woody.
I've known that guy my whole life. Two days!
Hey, did you know that Bonnie was not his first kid?
He had this other kid, Andy.
And you know what?
Hey, Lightyear.
Hey, up here, Astro-boy.
If you think you can just show up
and take our top prize spot...
- you're wrong! - Dead wrong!
You don't understand. I'm trying to...
Cheat the system and get with a kid. Yeah, we know.
No, I need...
A child to shower you with unconditional love?
Join the club, pal.
Yeah, join the club!
Come on, help me get outta here.
I'll help you. With my foot!
Get him.
Bunny, what are you doing?
I can't reach him. Help me out here, come on.
Sorry, Ducky. I'm not a mind reader, you know.
What's not to understand, hmm?
You gonna make me say it?
What?
With these tiny legs,
I cannot reach without your help.
Okay This is what
I've been talking about, Bunny.
You need to work on paying attention
and your listening skills.
How you like that, cheater?
Yeah!
To infinity and my foot! Boom!
In a galaxy far, far away, you got kicked in the head!
How do I get out of here?
This planet is toxic.
Closing helmet to conserve oxygen.
In the vacuum of space, they cannot hear you scream!
Let go of me!
Get off of me!
So, that's what gravity feel like.
Yeah, that's it.
Where you going?
You better get over here, spaceman!
Yeah, put us back up there!
Bunny, what are you doing? He's getting away, let's go!
- I'm trying! - Come on!
Antique store, here we come!
Bo, why do you ride around in a skunk?
Skunk!
A skunk!
I get it. Smart.
Corndogs, corndogs, corndogs!
Why are you so bad at driving?
You got six eyes.
Thanks for the landing.
Come on, follow me.
- I'm fine. - His face!
- That's hilarious. - I'm fine. Don't worry.
Happens all the time.
Tape!
Not a bad hiding spot.
Yeah. Leave the skunk.
- We'll fix it later. - 10-4.
This will be more fun.
Let's get you to that store!
Okay, spill it. The cowboy, what's the deal?
- There's no deal. - Uh-huh.
Don't do this to yourself. Cowboy's got a kid.
- Giggle... - Trust me. I've been there.
You know about me and He-Man. I'm not proud.
Here he comes!
- Oh, man... - What?
No, not you.
Second Chance Antiques, straight ahead.
Heavy foot traffic at the entrance.
- Easiest way in is...the roof. - The roof!
Let's go antiquing.
How did you end up here?
I thought you were given to a new family.
You know how it goes.
Their little girl grew up
and didn't need me anymore, so...
I'm sorry, Bo.
Who needs a kid's room...
when you can have all of this?
Whatcha looking at, Sheriff?
What? Oh, uh...
That wasn't... No, uh, nothing.
I was looking at the store. Right there.
I was looking at the antique store.
- Giggle, count us down. - Five.
- Countdown for what? - Four.
- You want to get to the store, don't you? - Three. Two. One!
The highway exit has to be somewhere.
Where is it?
Meteor shower! Look out!
Woody?
Good work, inner voice.
So, how about you? How's your new kid?
Bonnie? Oh, she's great.
Jessie is loving it.
Jessie's still with you?
Oh, yeah, the whole gang's still together.
Well, I mean, most of us.
What about Rex?
Yeah, yeah, Rex, Bullseye, Slinky...
- the Potato Heads... - Buzz?
Yeah, Buzz, too.
I cannot wait to see his face when he hears that I found...
- Bo Peep? - Buzz!
- My old moving buddy! - Buzz?
It's so good to see you!
Woody, it's Bo Peep!
- What are you doing here? - What are you doing here?
Buzz... Buzz... Buzz...
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
- Three years! - Three years!
That's how long we've been hanging up there
waiting for a kid!
Look, I'm sorry about that.
You ruined our lives. Shame on you!
Who are these guys?
- Lightyear promised us a kid. - You did what?
I did not.
- Wait a minute! - Eat my plush!
All right now, come on, stop it!
Cut it out now!
Come on, guys, break it up.
Guys, I have a kid!
You got a kid?
Like a kid-kid?
Like a human kid, not a baby goat?
Yeah. Now let go of Buzz and come with me.
I'll take you to Bonnie.
- We're gettin' a kid! - Yes!
We're gettin' a kid?
♪ We're gonna get a kid Kid ♪
- ♪ We're getting a kid ♪ - All right, let's go.
♪ We gonna get something, oh... ♪
- Where's Forky? - Long story.
♪ We gonna uh, uh, uh ♪
- ♪ Kid, we get a kid ♪ - ♪ Kid, kid, kid ♪
- ♪ We gonna kid? ♪ - ♪ We gonna kid, kid... ♪
He's not anywhere.
Forky's gone.
Honey, I'm sorry.
Okay. Let's look outside one more time.
But then we have to keep driving, okay?
They're about to leave!
- Leaving? - They can't do that!
The panic is attacking me!
- Watch it, buddy! - What do we do?
- We have to stop them! - How?
We could frame Dad for a crime so he goes to jail.
Or go back in time and warn Woody about the future.
That's crazy. Time is a flat circle.
Jessie!
I'm sorry, Bonnie.
We looked everywhere.
But we need to get going now, okay?
Can we please leave a note for Forky...
so he knows where we're going?
He has to go to kindergarten.
Are you kidding me, I can't...
Everything is going perfect... I just...
Okay! Daddy's going to use some words.
How about we go to the carnival?
Or maybe check out some of those shops in town?
What did you do?
We're not going anywhere.
- Brilliant! - That was genius!
Nice work, Jessie!
I'm sure Buzz and Woody are on their way back right now.
Forky is in there?
Yeah.
Now, hold on. I have a question.
Who will Bonnie love more? Ducky or me. Say me.
- No, say Ducky. Ducky. - Bunny. Bunny.
Okay, guys. Playtime is over.
You have to follow my lead.
We stay together, we stay quiet. Are we clear?
Absolutely. Lead the way.
- Are you kidding me. - Move over.
- You move over. - Quit pushing me.
Stop.
Oh, my maker! That sheep has three heads!
No, no, no!
What all six eyes just looked into my soul.
Gonna have nightmares.
That's most likely where your Forky is being kept.
All right, this isn't so bad.
We just can't be seen by the dummies.
Not just the dummies.
Her cabinet is surrounded by a moat of exposed aisle.
Where Dragon roams.
- We can handle a cat. - No.
Not this one.
Is that how we look on the inside?
There's so much... fluff.
So, how do you propose we get up there?
We could go straight across.
- How. - That's quite a jump.
We know the perfect toy to help.
Bonnie, check it out.
- Look at all this cool stuff. - Bonnie?
We got to get Forky now!
Woody, don't...
- Stick to the plan. - 10-4.
- Follow me. - Roger that.
Woody just sits in the closet? With no playtime?
Yeah, he told me himself, he's useless.
That's awful.
Such pretty hair...
What are you doing?
You need to stick to the plan.
But it's Bonnie. She's right...
Can we go to the carnival, too?
There.
Come on. Stay quiet.
You better hope the dummies didn't...
My sheep!
What did I say? I lead. You follow.
Bo, I'm so sorry. Really.
Just tell me how to help.
You really wanna help?
Then stay out of my way. I'm getting my sheep back.
What about the others?
Giggle knows what to do.
- Here you go. - That's our objective.
We have to get that key.
It's the only way inside the cabinet.
You can't be serious.
How are we supposed to do that?
Okay.
You know what, leave that to us.
We know exactly what to do.
Where did you two come from?
The keys! Give 'em up now! Where are they?
Give us the keys! Give us the keys!
Well, we're not doing that.
Yeah, yeah, I agree, too visible.
It's a good point. Something more subtle.
What about "winner, winner, chicken dinner"?
Yes.
The keys! Give 'em up now! Where are they?
- You're kidding. - Really?
Okay, okay. You just...
All right. Well...
What about the old "Plush Rush"?
There you go!
- Where is this going? - Don't interrupt.
Okay, right?
Not gonna happen. N-O.
Okay, do you want the key or not?
What is wrong with you?
What is wrong with...?
We just gave you three brilliant ideas.
It's one thing to say no.
It's another to offer a reason...
How do we get that key?
You're kidding!
Really?
Woody's back?
And you're sure it's Bo Peep who's with him?
Thank you, Benson.
Make sure the others are ready.
Woody's back!
I'm coming, Bonnie!
Bonnie.
First, we must prepare for his arrival.
Prepare?
Have you ever played hide-and-seek?
No. But it sounds complicated.
It's easy.
- I'll teach you, okay? - Okay.
The first thing you do is...
- one of us finds a place to hide... - Scary.
the other one...
What are we doing.
Just stand there and be quiet!
I'll do the talking.
Hi, Tinny!
Nice to see you, too.
Yeah, he's with me.
My friend? No, no, no.
He's my accessory.
- Hey, guys. - Bo!
Long time no see.
Couldn't take it out there, huh?
Hey, Doug. Saw your better half
at the front of the store.
Yeah, you mess with the cat, you get the claws.
Bo came back!
Magic 8-Ball was right!
- Excuse me. Sorry. - What are you doing here?
I thought the store had no return policy!
Bo, help me out.
I need a battery.
We got to get this wagon train a-movin'!
- Agreed. - Help, help, help.
Cheater.
Have you seen Duke?
He's in the back.
Look who jumped 40 school buses
and landed back into my life.
- Hi, Duke! - Who's the cowboy?
Duke, meet Woody. Woody, meet...
Duke Caboom. Canada's greatest stuntman.
Oh, yeah!
He's posing.
Duke?
- Duke, we need to... - Hold on. One more.
Yeah! What brings you back, Peep?
We need your help.
Gabby Gabby has his toy and my sheep.
No. Billy, Goat, and Gruff?
Those are my girls.
What were you doing getting tangled up with Gabby Gabby?
You know better.
Yeah, some toy thought it would be a good idea...
to wander into the aisle.
That doesn't make any sense.
It doesn't, does it?
Everybody knows the best route is behind the shelves.
That would have been a better route, wouldn't it?
This toy sounds like a complete idiot.
He does!
Wait, are you that toy?
So, here's the plan.
We need to jump over the aisle to Gabby's cabinet.
- And you are the toy to do it. - No.
- Duke. - Nope.
- Duke. - Never.
- Duke. - No way.
- Duke. - Pass.
- Duke. - Negative.
- Duke. - Rejected.
Please, Mr. Caboom, this is really important.
My kid...
You have a kid?
Hey, Duke, show us some more poses, what do you say?
- I had a kid. - Oh, no.
Rejean.
Rejean was so excited when he got me after Christmas.
It was the happiest Boxing Day of my life.
That's Duke Caboom,
riding the amazing Caboom stunt cycle!
Caboom!
I was ready to finally do what I was made to do.
But when Rejean realized I couldn't jump
as far as the toy in the commercial...
It's a commercial! It's not real!
Rejean threw me away!
It's not fair!
Why, Rejean Why?
Okay, okay. Calm down, Duke.
That was a long time ago.
Right now, we need the only toy
who can crash us onto Gabby's cabinet.
Crash?
Any Duke Caboom toy can land...
but you are the only one that can crash the way you do.
- I am? - Yes!
Forget Rejean. Forget your commercial.
Be the Duke you are right now...
the one who jumps and crashes!
Be who I am right now.
Who's the Canuck with all the luck?
Caboom?
Who's the greatest of the Great White North?
Caboom!
Who's the most spectacular daredevil Canada has ever seen?
Duke Caboom!
Can you do the jump?
Yes, I Canada!
We've got our ride.
Yee-haw!
Yo, Bo!
Gigs! You made it!
Good work!
How'd you get it?
How do we get that key?
- It was hard. - Very difficult.
- Barely made it out alive. - Yeah.
So, you're welcome.
Okay. Let's do this.
Let me wrap that up for you.
Don't want anything to happen to it on the way home.
Good. That sale buys us some time.
Wait for it.
All right, let's go!
So, how long were you in here?
I don't know. Couple years.
I didn't wanna sit on a shelf waiting for my life to happen.
So, I left.
You've handled this lost toy life better than I could.
Sheriff.
You're selling yourself short.
I think you'd make a great lost toy.
You really don't think
you'll ever be in a kid's room again, huh?
Nope.
And now with the carnival traveling through,
it's our chance to hop a ride...
- and leave town. - You're leaving?
Sure am.
You ever think about getting out there, seeing the world?
Without a kid?
No. You can't teach this old toy new tricks.
You'd be surprised.
So, how'd you end up in this store in the first place?
Well, I saw your lamp in the window...
and I thought maybe you were inside...
and so I, uh...
Will you look at that?
This is the only part of the store I ever liked.
That's gonna be quite a jump for you and Duke.
For me?
Didn't I tell you? You're going with him.
I am?
Let's caboom.
It'll be fine, Duke's the best.
Yeah, at crashing.
And now!
Go!
Rejean.
It's a commercial. It's not real!
I can't do this! I'm sorry, Rejean!
No, no, no!
What's new, pussycat?
- Forky? - Girls?
Forky, where are you?
You're never gonna find me.
Forky?
Woody! How'd you find me?
- Bo, I found him! - Hi.
Wait, it's an actual fork?
Bo! Bo! Bo!
Buzz! The dummies are gone!
What? Where'd they go?
Okay, we can go now!
- No. I need to find my girls. - Hello, Woody.
Hi, Bo.
- Where are my sheep - Yeah!
Look! Woody found me!
Take the bunny! I'm too cute to die!
No, no!
Woody!
I just wanna talk.
Yeah, with my voice box!
Pull!
You're my favorite deputy.
Somebody's poisoned the water hole.
I'd like to join your posse.
Reach for the sky!
Girls!
Drop it.
No! No! Forky!
- We've got to go! - Wait!
Forky!
Woody!
Bonnie's backpack?
Giggle!
Don't let Woody leave!
Grab on!
Duke, get us out of here!
Oui!
Here, kitty, kitty!
Wait! We don't have Forky!
Woody!
Forky!
Is everyone okay?
- It's okay. - It's okay.
Bunny? Bunny!
Bunny! No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
- Bunny! - It's gonna be okay.
Forky's still in there.
If we hurry,
we can get him before they lock him up.
You want us to go back in there?
We barely got out alive.
Woody, it's better if we wait.
No, no, no. There's no time. We can easily get back inside.
But I saw Bonnie's...
By my count, there were only four dummies.
But the backpack...
We outnumber them. So we have the advantage.
Woody, look at us!
Nobody is with you. It's over, okay?
No. No, no, no. We are wasting time. We can do this.
- Come on, Pull-string. - It's not worth it.
Yeah, yes, listen to her!
- Nobody wants this! - I do!
- Why? - Because!
- Why? - Just because!
Why?
Because it's all I have left to do!
I don't have anything else.
So, the rest of us don't count?
That's not what I meant.
Bonnie needs Forky.
No. You need Bonnie!
Open your eyes, Woody.
There's plenty of kids out there.
It can't be just about the one you're still clinging to.
It's called loyalty.
Something a lost toy wouldn't understand.
I'm not the one who's lost.
Let's get out of here.
We've got a carnival that leaves in the morning.
Come on.
We'll find our own kid.
You're crazy.
Bo!
Bye, Woody. Good luck with Bonnie.
Woody, you did all you could.
Time to go home.
No.
- Woody. - I don't leave toys behind, Buzz.
Yeah, but, Woody, you're actually leaving...
Not now. Not ever.
And he left me behind.
What now, inner voice?
Mission accomplished. Return to base.
Go back to the RV? What about Woody?
We're going home, space ranger.
Fall back, this planet...
Retreat! There's too...
Go! Time to fly! Exit the... Back... Run...
Get out! Returning to Star Command.
Okay. Okay.
Thanks a lot, inner voice.
Harmony, honey, help Grandma close up for the night.
Okay. Then can we go to the carnival?
Sure.
Hello, Woody.
I knew you'd be back.
You don't know me.
But I do.
You were left in the closet, feeling useless...
wondering if you'll ever get played with.
I'm not leaving without Forky.
Can we agree on just one thing?
What?
That being there for a child
is the most noble thing a toy can do.
Okay.
I was defective right out of the box.
I can only imagine what it must have been like for you.
All that time you spent with Andy...
riding a bike with him for the first time...
comforting him when he skinned his knee...
proudly watching him grow up.
And then you got a second chance with Bonnie...
giving her comfort when she's scared at school...
helping her when she needs it most.
You've been there through all their ups and downs.
Please.
Be honest with me.
Was it as wonderful as it sounds?
It was.
All I want is a chance for just one of those moments.
I'd give anything to be loved the way you have.
Just leave me Forky.
Bonnie needs him.
Of course.
The flat tire is fixed!
Come on, Woody, hurry up.
Where is he?
- Buzz! - Buzz!
- Where's Woody? - And Forky?
We have a situation.
They need to be extracted from the antique store.
How do we do that?
Okay, let's make sure we have everything.
Finally.
It's okay.
Any minute now... Bonnie will notice her backpack is missing.
She'll realize she left it at the antique store...
and we'll head back in there.
Okay. Looks like we have everything.
- You good, Bonnie? - Yup.
Great. Let's get out of here.
Okay, genius, what do we do now?
Scanning perimeter.
Laser at full power!
- Buzz, what are you doing? - I'm thinking.
Honey, will you please shut that toy off?
Yeah, I got it.
Attack! Meteor shower! Look out!
It's a secret mission in uncharted space!
Let's go!
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
- Bonnie, how do you turn this off? - Full speed ahead!
- Open the pod bay doors! - I don't know.
It's just you and me now, cadet.
A distress signal is coming from that rocket.
Just toss it in the drawer.
To infinity and beyond!
Your backpack's in the antique store! Let's go!
Oh, no, my backpack!
I left my backpack in the antique store!
You did?
All right, let's swing by and get it.
I can't believe the nerve of that cowboy.
I mean, who does he think he is?
Exactly!
He was way out of line.
You did the right thing leaving him behind.
Lamb Chops?
Coast is clear.
Head to the middle.
When the carnival leaves tomorrow,
we'll hide right there.
- No way! - Stuff that.
Awesome.
Stick with me. You'll be fine.
- Ready? - No!
And another thing,
- Woody asked you for help. - On your mark...
And he treats you like that?
- Get set... - He only cares about himself.
No!
You're wrong.
Woody's always trying to do right by his kid.
By putting everyone in danger.
That kind of crazy loyalty just...
You got to love him for it.
Say what now?
Bo! What's the plan?
Fill me in here.
Get in! We're going back.
We just got here.
You heard Bo! We're going back!
Move your plush! Let's ride!
You're my favorite...
Yay!
You are my best friend.
Let's play all day!
Benson! Did you hear that?
Isn't that lovely?
Time for tea.
Thank you, Woody. Thank you!
All my dreams are coming true because of you.
Thank you! Thank you!
You're welcome.
It's time, Benson.
Goodbye, Forky. I'm going to miss our talks.
Me, too. Good luck, Gabby.
Thank you, my little utensil.
Bye, Gabby! Goodbye, Benson!
He is terrifying.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Bonnie? - Can I help you with anything?
Yeah. We called about the backpack.
Yes. I couldn't find it.
Feel free to look around.
Quick! Before she finds it!
Look! There's Harmony.
You make me so happy!
Let's be best friends.
This is it!
We're going home, Forky!
Forky!
No, no, no. Woody, look! It's really happening!
I'm Gabby Gabby, and I love you.
I'm gonna cry.
What have you got there?
I found this old doll.
You can take it home if you want.
Nah.
What happened? Gabby was supposed to be her toy.
There's my backpack!
Mom, it's over here.
Forky!
Mom, I found him!
There he is!
Now, please leave him in there,
so he doesn't get lost again.
But what about Gabby?
Forky, listen to me very carefully.
This is important.
Tell Buzz to get the RV to the merry-go-round.
You understand?
Absolutely. What is a merry-go-round?
The spinny ride with lights and horses.
- You mean a carousel. - Yes!
Carousel. Yes! Meet me at the carousel.
Got it.
Gabby! Gabby!
You can have your voice box back.
I don't need it anymore.
Yes, you do.
Harmony wasn't your only chance, Gabby,
but we have to hurry. Come on.
No. Harmony was my chance.
My time's over.
Now, please go away.
You hear that?
A friend once told me...
"There are plenty of kids out there."
And one of them is named Bonnie.
She's waiting for you, right now.
She just doesn't know it yet.
What if you're wrong?
Well, if you sit on a shelf the rest of your life...
you'll never find out, will you?
He's right.
I learned that from the best.
Come on, Gabby.
Let's get you to Bonnie.
The carousel?
Yeah, it's the spinny ride with lights and horses.
Woody said to meet him there.
- You got to be kidding! - How do we do that?
We could...
We are not sending Dad to jail.
You're no fun.
Left turn in 0.5 miles.
Wait a second. I have an idea.
Skunk!
Too many people. Gonna need an alternate route.
Will we make it to the carousel in time?
Yes, we Canada!
What? What is it?
Recalculating. Take a right.
What? A right?
Right turn ahead.
Does the GPS sound funny to you?
Honey, it's fine. Just drive.
I thought it sounded funny.
Another right!
- Right. - Take another right.
Another right, really?
- Turn right! - Now!
Turn right!
- We're headin' back. - There's the carousel!
Do you think Woody will get there in time?
Nope. Forget it. Never. No. No way. Declined.
- No dice. Rejected. - Duke, Duke, you got this.
This is the fastest way to the carousel.
You made the last jump.
Yeah, but that was 4 feet. This is 40!
Exactly! Duke Caboom would never repeat a stunt.
- No. He'd never do that. - No, no, no.
He's the toy that went on to crash 40 feet
into that target!
Yeah, he is.
I'm Duke Caboom!
Oh, man. I can do this!
Yes, you Canada!
I can do it with my eyes closed.
Yes, you... What?
- Three, two, one. Go! - What! No, wait!
- What is he doing? - Oh, no.
This is for you, Rejean.
Caboom.
Yes!
He did it!
All right, our turn!
You heard the sheriff. Let's go.
Another right!
Another right? That's the wrong way.
- Are you sure? - Stupid rental.
- I'm turning us around. - No!
Recalculating.
Turn right.
- Must be broken. - No! No!
What is happening?
Honey, what are you doing? Slow down!
I can't! I can't!
- Press the brake. - I'm trying.
Press it!
Got a visual on the RV, heading southbound.
Gabby?
I think she's lost.
Are you sure?
Change of plans.
Pull over.
I can't! This is a rental!
I don't know what's happening!
I'm so nervous.
- What if she doesn't like me? - Gabby.
I don't know if I can do this.
Gabby, it's just like you said.
This is the most noble thing a toy can do.
Okay. Just edge yourself a bit into the light.
Not too far.
That's it.
Perfect.
Winner, winner... Chicken dinner.
Are you lost, too?
I'm Gabby Gabby. Will you be my friend?
I'll help you.
Excuse me, can you... Can you help us?
Honey, what's wrong?
I can't find my mom and dad.
It's okay. I'll help you find them.
I'm sure they're not far.
She was right next to us.
She was right here!
And I looked away for one second.
Mommy!
I couldn't find you...
and then I found this doll.
You did?
Her name is Gabby Gabby.
We actually did that.
- Oh, yeah. - Yes!
That was amazing.
We make a great team, guys.
Pull over now!
Almost there.
- Stop! - Stop!
Are we home?
Sir, will you please step out of the vehicle?
Dad's totally going to jail.
Everyone, topside. Let's move.
Forky, I've got a very important job for you.
For me?
Have a good night.
What the...?
You've got to be kidding me.
So long, cowboy.
Happy trails.
Billy, Goat, Gruff. Take care of her, girls.
I'm glad I got to see you again.
I... I don't...
Goodbye, Bo.
Buzz, I... I...
She'll be okay.
Bonnie will be okay.
You sure?
Listen to your inner voice.
Bo?
Is it really her?
I'll be danged, it's Bo!
Jessie.
Bo!
So long, Forky.
Forky! Who's watching the doors?
- Go, go, go! - Oh, boy.
Oh, my goodness. The awning. What is going on?
Does this mean Woody's a lost toy?
He's not lost.
Not anymore.
- To infinity... - And beyond.
There goes another one.
We're never getting outta here.
Frog legs.
Up here, Rainbow Connection.
You Mr. Toads wanna take a wild ride with a kid?
We can make that happen.
- You can? - Really?
Oh, yeah! Leave it to us, Jeremiah.
All right. Nice job, gang!
Every prize with a kid.
- What's next - Leave that to us.
We know exactly what to do.
Plush Rush!
How you like that, huh?
You got plush-rushed, son!
Dance!
Dance! Get those knees up!
Let's see those feet move!
Or we can get more toys to kids.
Yeah, let's do that.
Do you really have laser eyes?
Yeah.
Hi, toys. Bye, toys.
Jessie's back!
What's first grade like? Tell me everything!
Well, it was...
How was "Present and Explain"?
You mean "Show and Tell" there, big guy.
You see any kids eat paste?
Guys, listen!
Bonnie had a great day in first grade.
She even made a new friend in class.
She's already making friends.
No, no, she made a new friend.
Come on out, it's okay.
Hi. I'm, uh... I'm Forky.
Trash?
No, no. Toy. I am a... We are all toys.
Unique, beautiful toys.
I will explain everything.
How am I alive?
I don't know.
The Ballad of the Lonesome Cowboy - Chris Stapleton
♪ I was a lonesome cowboy ♪
♪ Lonesome as I could be ♪
♪ You came along and changed my life ♪
♪ And fixed what was broken in me ♪
♪ I was a lonesome cowboy ♪
♪ I didn't have a friend ♪
♪ Now I got friends coming out of my ears ♪
♪ I'll never be lonesome again ♪
♪ You can't be happy when you're all by yourself ♪
♪ Go on, tell me I'm wrong? ♪
♪ You're wrong ♪
♪ When someone takes you down from the shelf ♪
♪ And plays with you some It's wonderful ♪
♪ Wonderful? ♪
♪ I was a lonesome cowboy ♪
♪ But not anymore ♪
♪ I just found out what love is about ♪
♪ I've never felt this way before ♪
♪ I was a lonesome cowboy ♪
? But not anymore ?